A Finding Aid to the Ben Shahn Papers, 1879-1990, bulk 1933-1970, in the Archives of American Art AAA.shahben
Archives of American Art
- Letters, 1929-1990; Series 2; 14.4 Linear feet Boxes 1-25, 35, OVs 36-38
  - Barr, Roger, 1956-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Baskin, Esther and Leonard (Gehenna Press), 1953-1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    (includes letter and notes from Shahn)
  - Beerman, Leonard I. and Martha, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Benrus Watch Company, Inc., (Bond, Harvey M.), 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bentivoglio, Mirella, 1958-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Berkowitz, Rosalie and Sidney, circa 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bezalel National Museum, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bianchi Gallery, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Biddle, George, circa 1948-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Biel-Bienne, Eugene V., 1959-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bill Bagnall Associates, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Birthday Greeting Telegrams to Shahn, 1968 September 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Black Mountain College, 1950-1952 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Block, Lou and Mary, 1942-1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Blumenthal, Joseph, see: Spiral Press (Box 4)
  - Bone, Mary and Stephen, 1953-1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Boris Mirski Gallery, 1956-1961, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Boston Arts Festival, 1953-1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Boston Public Library, 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Boston University, 1956-1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Brandeis University, 1954-1968, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Brattiga, P., Jr., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bressler, Martin, 1954, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bressler, Martin, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bressler, Martin, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bressler, Martin, 1969-1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Brewster, Joan, circa 1930s-1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Briggs, Austin, 1952-1961 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation (Humphrey Burton), 1959-1965, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Britten, Barbara and Roy J., 1949-1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1951-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Brown University (including Pembroke College), 1953-1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Bryson, Charles H., 1936-1948 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Bucknell University, 1968, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Burrows, Selig S., 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bush, Martin H. (see also Syracuse University), 1964-1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - B, Miscellaneous: B. - Ban, 1945-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bar - Bay, 1947-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    (includes letter from Shahn to Mr. Baskerville re. commercial commissions)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bea - Ben, 1947-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Ber - Bet, 1947-1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bi - Bl, 1945-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bn - Bo, 1948-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bra - Bri, 1950-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bro - Bry, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Buc - Buo, 1953-1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bur - By, 1953-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    (includes letter from Shahn to Don Luis re. work of Jos Buscaglia)
  - B, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - B, First Names Only, circa 1940s-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - B, Illegible, circa 1950s (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Calder, Alexander, circa 1949-1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    (includes illustrated letters)
  - Calder, Alexander, 1958-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Capitol Records, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Carleton College, 1959-1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Carlisle, John C., 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1945-1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Carroll, Mark (see also Harvard University Press), circa 1948-1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Caruso, Bruno (see also Obelisco Galleria d'Arte), circa 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Casetta, Mario ("Boots"), 1949-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chamberlain, Betty (Betty Chamberlain Associates), circa 1944-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Charles E. Slatkin Collections of Contemporary Tapestries and Sculptures - Modern Master Tapestries, Inc., 1972-1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Charles E. Slatkin, Inc., Galleries, 1959, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Charles E. Tuttle Co., Inc., 1961-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1959-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Charm, circa 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Review, 1954-1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Christian Scholar, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - City of New York, 1935, 1960-1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Clauss, Alfred (Sepel), 1947-1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland Institute of Art, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cloutier, Albert, 1942-1958 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Coe College, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Coen, Fabio and Silvane, circa 1956-1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Cohen, H. Hirsch, 1951-1955 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Colby Junior College, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - College Art Association of America, 1935-1954 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1952-1967 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Columbia Records, 1954-1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Columbia University (including Teachers College and Columbia University Press), 1950-1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Cone, Edward T., 1958-1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Conference on the Status of Soviet Jews, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Congregation B'nai Jeshurun, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Congregation Mishkan Israel, 1957-1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Congregation Ohabi Sholom, 1959-1969 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    (includes letter from Shahn regarding mosaic mural)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations Political Action Committee (CIO-PAC), circa 1944-1952 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    (includes statement regarding a project with Murray, Hillman and Baldwin, possibly written by Shahn)
  - Conklin, Groff and Lucy, 1938-1960 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Contact, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Container Corporation of America, 1945-1967 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1941-1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Crafton Graphic Company, Inc., 1952-1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Crossroads Books, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Crown Publishers, Inc., 1952-1965 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cummings, Mildred and Willard (Bill), circa 1950s-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus and Mitzi, 1955-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - C, Miscellaneous: C. - Ca, 1949-1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Ce, 1954-1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    contains artwork
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cha, 1952-1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Che - Chu, 1944-1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Ci - Cl, 1941-1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cob - Coi, 1945-1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Col - Com, 1948-1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cond - Cong, 1949-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Conn - Coo, 1953-1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cop - Cor, 1951-1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cos - Coy, 1936-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cr, 1947-1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cu, 1947-1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - C, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - C, First Names Only, circa 1949-1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - C, Illegible, circa 1950s-1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - DNP (America), Inc., 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Daedalus, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dahlberg, Edward, 1955-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dartmouth College, 1952-1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Daves, L. Joan, circa 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - De Arbeiderspers, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - de Koven, Daniel, circa 1950-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - De Pauw University, 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Del Guercio, Antonio, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Delacorte Press, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Delpire, Robert (Nouvel Observateur), 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Democratic State Central Committee (Michigan), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Despres, Leon M. and Marian, 1948-1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    (includes 1958 letter from Shahn)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1951-1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Dombrowski, James A.: see Southern Conference Educational Fund (Box 8)
  - Donahue & Co., Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Dorsky, Morris, circa 1948-1965 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Downtown Gallery, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Downtown Gallery, 1944-1952 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Downtown Gallery, 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Downtown Gallery, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Gallery, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Gallery, 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Drawing Society, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - D, Miscellaneous: D' - Da, 1953-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - D, Miscellaneous: De, 1946-1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - D, Miscellaneous: Di, 1948-1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - D, Miscellaneous: Do-Dw, 1955-1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    (includes illustrated letter from Henry Dreyfuss)
  - D, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - D, First Names Only, 1954-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - D, Illegible, 1958-1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - E. P. Dutton & Co., Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Eastman, John (Jack) (see also: Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture), circa 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Eberhart, Richard, 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Editions d'Art Lucien Mazenod, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Edmunds, John, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Educational Alliance, 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation, 1963-1966, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Edward, Gladys and Harry, 1945-1957 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Edward MacDowell Association, Inc., 1953-1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - El Al Israel Airlines, 1956-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1952-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    (includes letters from Shahn)
  - Encyclopedia Judaica Press, Inc./Encyclopedia Judaica Research Foundation, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Engel, Monroe, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Esquire Magazine, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Eva Lee Gallery, 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Evans, Clifford, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Evans, Ernestine, 1935-1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Evans, Walker, 1929, circa 1961-1962, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Evergood, Philip, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - E, Miscellaneous: Ea - Ed, 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - E, Miscellaneous: Ei - En, 1943-1959 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - E, Miscellaneous: Er - Es, 1952-1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    (includes letter from Ruth Erskine to Shahn enclosing an etching by Shahn)
  - E, Miscellaneous: Eu - Ex, 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - E, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - E, First Names Only, 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Famous Artists Schools, Inc., circa 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    (includes scattered letters from Shahn, circa 1953-1969)
  - Famous Artists Schools, Inc., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Famous Artists Schools, Inc., 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Famous Artists Schools, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Famous Artists Schools, Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Famous Artists Schools, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Farrar, Straus and Cudahy, Inc., 1955-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Fawcett, Robert (Westport Artists), 1955-circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Fawcus, Arnold: see Trianon Press (Box 11)
  - Ferry, W. H. (Ping), (see also War/Peace Report), circa 1944-1954 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ferry, W. H. (Ping), circa 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Ferry, W. H. (Ping), 1957-1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Festival Foundation Inc.: see Menotti, Gian Carlo (Box 11)
  - Finkelstein, Louis (Jewish Theological Seminary of America), 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fleischman, Barbara and Lawrence A., 1954-1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Flint Institute of Arts, 1945, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Fogg Museum, circa 1948-1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    (includes notes from Shahn circa 1949-1968)
  - Fogg Museum, 1957-1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fogg Museum (see also Harvard University Art Museums), 1969-1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    (letters reference disposition of Shahn's photographic archives to the Fogg Museum)
  - Forbes, Kenneth Ripley, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation, 1958-1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Foreman, Clark and Shelagh, circa 1948-1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Fortune, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Fossum, Bunny and Syd, 1950-1954, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Franois, Andr and Margaret, circa 1958-1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    (includes illustrated letter)
  - Frank, Lewis C., Jr., 1947-1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Fraser, Donald M., 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Fratelli Fabbri Editori, 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Frauwirth, Jean and Sidney, circa 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Friedman, Charlotte and Sam, circa 1956-1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Friendly, Dorothy G. and Fred W., circa 1956-1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - F, Miscellaneous: F. - Fa, 1954-1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fe, 1945-1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fi, 1952-1968 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fl - Fo, 1946-1969 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fra - Fre, 1958-1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fre - Fu, 1948-1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - F, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Gad, Dora, 1963-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Gallery 63 Inc., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gash, Emily Genauer, 1952-1969, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    (includes 1976 illustrated letter by Bernarda Bryson Shahn)
  - Gash, Frederick, circa 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Gassner, Nathan, Browne, Architects, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Gemini G.E.L., 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Georg Jensen Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - George Braziller, Inc., 1948-1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - George Braziller, Inc., 1959-1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Gnoli, Annie de Garrou, 1969-1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Goldburg, Robert E. (see also Congregation Mishkan Israel), circa 1959-circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Goodman, Percival, 1947-1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    (includes 1966 letters from Shahn to Goodman regarding Shahn's procedures for mural work)
  - Gould, Joseph, 1954-1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Graham, Louise, 1955-1967 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Graphis, 1947-1965, 1973-1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Grippi Gallery (formerly Gallery "G"), circa 1955-1967 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Grossman Publishers, Inc. (Richard L. Grossman), circa 1961-1970 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Grunbaum, James, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Gusten, Chaja and Theodore, circa 1951-circa 1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Gutman, Judith Maria, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - G, Miscellaneous: G. - Gal, 1936-1969 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gam - Gay, 1957-1967 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Ge - Gh, 1950-1968 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gi, 1950-1968 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gl - Gol, 1948-1969 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Goo - Gov, 1947-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    (includes letter from Carolyn Goodman re. Shahn's drawings of Andrew Goodman, James Chaney, and Michael Schwerner)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gra - Gree, 1951-1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Greg - Gru, 1954-1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Gu - Gw, 1949-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - G, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - G, First Names Only, 1954-1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - G, Illegible, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Halpert, Edith Gregor, see: Downtown Gallery (Box 13)
  - Har Zion Temple, 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Harling, Robert, circa 1950s-1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Harper & Row, Incorporated, 1950-1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Harper's Magazine, Inc., 1947-1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Harry N. Abrams, Incorporated, circa 1957-1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Harvard College Library (Philip Hofer), circa 1950-1960, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Harvard University (various departments), circa 1950-1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Harvard University (various departments), 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Harvard University Art Museums, 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Harvard University Press, circa 1956-1965 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Harvard University Press, 1966-1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Haverford College, 1956-1964 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion, 1964-1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Heibonsha Ltd., 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Heller Deltah Co., Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - High School of Music and Art, 1948-1964 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Hill and Wang, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Hill Publishing Company, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Hirsch, Elsa and Stefan, 1936-1954 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Hofstra College, 1955-1961 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    (includes typescript of May 1961 symposium with Ben Shahn, James Baldwin and Darius Milhaud)
  - Holland, Reginald H., circa 1947-1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1964-1975, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hope, Henry Radford, 1949-1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Horwitt, Nathan George, 1957-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - House of H. Heydenryk, Jr., 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Howell, Douglas, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hudson, Richard: see War/Peace Report (Box 14)
  - H, Miscellaneous: H. - Han, 1947-1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Han - Har, 1943-1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    (includes illustrated letter and handwritten music composition by Lou Harrison)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Has - Haz, 1949-1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - H, Miscellaneous: He, 1950-1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hi, 1944-1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    (includes 4 letters from Joseph Hirsch and 2 from Joseph Hirshhorn)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hl - Hoo, 1949-1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hop - Hoy, 1947-1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hu - Hy, 1952-1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - H, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1969-1988 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - H, First Names Only, circa 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - H, Illegible, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Imbrie, James and Nell, circa 1949-1967, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Insel-Verlag, 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Religious and Social Studies, 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1947-1965, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, Washington, D.C., 1956-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Institute of International Education, 1950-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - International Biennial Exhibition of Prints in Tokyo, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - International Congress on Religion, Architecture and the Visual Arts (1967), 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - International Design Conference in Aspen, 1951-1966 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - International Graphic Arts Society, Inc. (IGAS), circa 1951-1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - International Graphic Arts Society, Inc. (IGAS), 1954-1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - International Graphic Arts Society, Inc. (IGAS), 1959-1969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, 1938-1961 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - International Poster Annual, 1948-1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ivan Obolensky, Inc. (see also Coen, Fabio), 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - I, Miscellaneous: I. - Ins, 1945-1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - I, Miscellaneous: Int, 1953-1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - I, Miscellaneous: Io - Iz, 1951-1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - I, Miscellanous, Posthumous, 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - I, First Names Only, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Jaffe, Marie B., 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Jamesine Franklin School of Professional Arts, Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Museum, 1960-1976 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Jewish News, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 1947-1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1954-1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1970, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Joseph Devernay Contemporary Art, 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Juhl, Finn and Hanne, 1963-1970 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Julian Levy Gallery, circa 1940 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Julien, Andree, circa 1955-1969 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    (includes illustrated greeting card)
  - Jung, Theodor, 1944-1962 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - J, Miscellaneous: J. - Ja, 1931-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - J, Miscellaneous: Je, 1948-1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ji - Jo, 1948-1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - J, Miscellaneous: Ju, 1942-1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - J, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1979-1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - J, First Names Only, 1941-1966 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Kahler, Eric, circa 1946-1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Kahn and Jacobs, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kaplan, Doug, circa 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    (includes original artwork by Kaplan)
  - Kearns, Betty and James J., circa 1955-1969, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy Galleries, Inc., 1957-1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Kent, Corita, circa 1953-1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Kent State University, 1951-1952, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Kerney, Lincoln and Mary and Family, circa 1960-1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1935-1952 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Klein, Sam, circa 1960-1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Klemin, Diana: see Doubleday and Company, Inc. (Box 16)
  - Kyodo News Services, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - K, Miscellaneous: K. - Kam, 1949-1968 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Kan - Kay, 1937-1968 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Ke, 1949-1968 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Ki, 1947-1967 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Kl - Kn, 1937-1968 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Ko - Ku, 1954-1969 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - K, Miscellaneous, Posthumous, 1971-1988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - K, First Names Only, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - K, Illegible, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Ladejinsky, Wolf (Ford Foundation), circa 1960-1967 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Landau Gallery, 1956-1968 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Lange, Dorothea, circa 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Larkin, Oliver W., 1948-1956 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Lazrus, Jay Kay, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Lear Publishers, Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - LeMoyne College, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Levy, Peter L., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congress, 1950-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Life, 1937-1938, 1951-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1962-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Linea Grafica, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Lionni, Leo and Nora, circa 1958-1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Little, Brown and Company, circa 1958-1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Loire Imports, Inc. (Gabriel Loire), 1967-1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Look, circa 1951-1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Lord, James, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Louis de Rochemont Associates, Inc., 1954-1958 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ludgin, Earle and Mary, 1952-1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lutheran Society for Worship, Music and the Arts, 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Lyons, Leonard and Sylvia ( New York Post), 1959-1969 (Box 17, Folder 15)